# **Neil GOODRIDGE**

**FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER** 

+447809 489899

neilrgoodridge@gmail.com

neilgoodridge

neilgoodridge

Wimbledon, London

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a committed learner having spent 6 months of evening and weekends studying and retraining alongside my full time job at the highly regarded Le Wagon bootcamp in London. I'm looking forward to transferring the skills I have learned in my current and previous roles and pairing them with those I've learned over the last few months in an engineering role.

I'm currently a Regional Business Manager for Subway London, with 10+ years of management experience in the hospitality sector at many levels and companies, all including heading major system changes from scheduling, recruitment and training to rolling out major regional initiatives such as third-party delivery most recently.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Ruby, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript
- HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap
- Databases, SQL and Postgresql
- · Minitest Rails, Yarn package manager
- Git and Github
- Heroku

#### **PROJECTS**

## The OA 🔀

An Online Activism platform, built with Ruby on Rails using MVC pattern • Designed DB schema • Wrote 90% of the front end • Presented to class.

## WaterRnR 🗹

Host your own pool, or rent someone else's in your area. Built using RoR, incorporating TypeScript, jQuery and basic CRUD actions.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Le Wagon - London, Batch #525 (2021)

25-week part time intensive web development bootcamp learning Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, SQL, ES6, Heroku and Github.

#### Hellesdon College (2002)

4 A-levels in Chemistry, Economics, Religious Studies and Philosophy.

#### **Hellesdon High School**

10 GCSEs.

#### INTERESTS

Home Cinema, Formula 1, Playing guitar, Road cycling, Football, Rugby, Gardening, Travelling, Cooking, European & American History.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Subway Development Office | Greater London Regional Business Manager | December 2018 - Present

- Leading a team of up to 9 Business Consultants responsible for up to 264 stores' operations at a London-wide level.
- Member of the Third-Party Delivery Steering Group for the UK, tasked with rollout and ongoing improvement of the program.
- Led the London region into third-party delivery in 2018-19 that added an average of 24% to stores P&L and kept them afloat through 2020's lockdowns.
- Put together the main content for our annual conferences and presented this to around 230 people (internal and external).

### **Business Consultant** | August 2016 - November 2018

- Regular meetings with stores and franchise owners for brand standards checks.
- P&L reviews, hands-on training.
- Researching potential new locations.

#### Greggs | April 2015-July 2016

#### Floating General Manager, London (South East)

- Accountable for P&L for 3 stores in South East London.
- Training of the teams up to 12 per store.
- Turned around Lewisham store from -£5k pw to +£4k in 5 months.
- Implemented online scheduling system.

## McDonald's 2008 - March 2015

### Assistant Manager, Norwich Airport

- General P&L responsibilities in support of the General Manager.
- Led largest update of McDonald's internal systems for 3 stores.
- Weekly scheduling for up to 115 people.
- Boosted Apprenticeship program completions by 40% YoY.